<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Just Coding</title>
    <link>https://nkcoder.github.io/categories/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Just Coding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 07:31:28 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nkcoder.github.io/categories/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>商务口语集锦四</title>
      <link>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 07:31:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-4/</guid>
      <description>- I think you should look over these figures again. 我想你应该再把这些数字核实一遍 - There are some calculations that are a bit off. 有些计算不太确切 - He&amp;#39;d like to know if you can send over those training manuals? 他想知道您能否将那些培训手册发过去？ - Oh, tell him I&amp;#39;ll leave them at his office tomorrow afternoon. 噢，告诉他明天下午我把它们送到他的办公室 - I hate to do this to you, Alice, but I&amp;#39;m going to have to ask you to put in some more overtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>商务口语集锦三</title>
      <link>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 07:27:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-3/</guid>
      <description>- Can you all take a look at your schedules? 你们能看看你们的日程安排吗？ - Thursday mornings are usually the slowest around here. 星期四上午总是这儿最闲的时候。 - We&amp;#39;re going to need everybody&amp;#39;s input on this project. So I&amp;#39;d like to fix a time to meet next week and hear what you all have to say. 我们需要大家同心协力地投入到这个项目中来. 因此我想和大家定时间在下周开个会，听取各位的意见 - I do not have any problem with that. Let&amp;#39;s set it up for 9:30 Wednesday morning. We can carry it over to Thursday if we need to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>商务口语集锦二</title>
      <link>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 21:55:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-2/</guid>
      <description>- I just started a couple of weeks ago. 我几周前刚开始工作 - Well, if there is anything I can do for you, let me know. 如果有什么我能帮忙的，尽管开口 - When would you like me to send those plans over to your office? 你要我什么时候把这些计划送到你的办公室？ - It would be good if you could get them to me by Thursday afternoon. 你最好能在周四之前把他们交给我 - That&amp;#39;ll be ahead of schedule! Good work. 这样就比计划提前了 - Well, as the saying goes: we aim to please!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>商务口语集锦一</title>
      <link>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 21:53:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nkcoder.github.io/posts/english/business-speaking-selected-1/</guid>
      <description>- take the subway 坐地铁 - take the bus 乘公交车 - Thanks for the advice, I&amp;#39;ll keep it in mind. 谢谢你的建议，我会记住的 - I had better head off though. 不过我得赶紧走了 - Sure, I&amp;#39;m heading out myself. 好，我也得走了 - Enjoy your evening. 祝晚上愉快 - Thanks for the warning. 谢谢你的提醒 - I&amp;#39;ve got a ton of stuff on my desk. 我桌上压成吨的活了 - But I&amp;#39;m really not in a position to make a decision right now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
